It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can you see it?
見えそうですか?
Let's take off your breasts for a moment.
ちょっとじゃあおっぱい外しちゃいましょうか
What is this?
なんだこれは?
She has beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいしてる
What do you think?
なんと思うの?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Just a little...
ちょっとじゃあ...
amazing.
すごい
He'll touch you right away.
すぐ触ってくれるじゃん
I was curious.
気になっちゃった
Are you curious?
気になっちゃった?
I was curious.
気になっちゃった
I've been hooked ever since that moment.
あった瞬間からビンビンなんだけど
lie?
嘘?
Really?
本当に?
TRUE?
本当?
Oh, I'm happy.
え、嬉しい
Have you ever seen Chin Chin?
チンチン見たことある?
there is.
あります
Let's have a look.
見てもらおう
get nervous.
緊張する
Isn't it really big?
めっちゃ大きくないですか?
It's really big.
め っちゃ大きい
kind.
優しい
When it starts to hurt, it's sunny.
痛くなっちゃったら晴れたから
It's really big.
すごい大きい
You're good at it.
上手だね
Really?
本当に?
happy.
嬉しい
Over here.
こっちで
A little bitter.
ちょっと苦い
delicious?
美味しい?